前情回顾
Previously on "Power"
- 老板来了 - 这是今年
- Boss is here. - This is the best
最棒的夜店开幕庆典
Goddamn nightclub opening the whole year.
- 敬真理 - 真理!
- To truth! - Truth!
我们初次见面时
When we met,
你觉得我会成为什么样的人?
who'd you think I was gonna be?
纽约的贩毒老大
The biggest goddamn drug dealer in new york city.
你想保护的那个人
The men you're protecting
让你今晚
Sent you out to steal
来偷一群不该惹的人
From the wrong motherfuckers tonight.
如果我知道是谁指使的
If I knew who ordered it,
这人绝对不会活到现在
Yeah, they'd be dead already.
五万
50 stacks.
你把他活着带来就给你七万五
75 if you bring him to us alive.
你知道不能因任何缘由影响我们的交易
It's good to see that you know enough
这样很好
Not to let it affect our pay schedule.
安吉拉・巴尔德斯昨晚来夜店了
Angela Valdes came into the club last night.
高中的那个?
From high school?
杰米 当年的事我很抱歉
Jamie, I'm sorry I left the way I did.
谁能提供我们需要的人名 地点和日期
Who can give us the names, places, and dates we need
来指控洛沃斯?
To convict Lobos?
他的纽约经销商
His new york distributor.
不幸的是 我们根本不知道他是谁
Unfortunately, we have no idea who that is.
我们的人都装备好了 我们应该也是
Our soldiers are strapped now. We should be too.
我把电梯停了
I stopped the elevator.
我们到了
We're here.
伤得重吗?
It's bad?
我女朋友... 她刚刚被抢劫了
My girlfriend... she just got mugged.
劫匪逃了
Guy got away.
拜托 请你安排一辆救护车
Please, please send an ambulance.
汤米 什么事?
Tommy, what's up?
胡里奥有紧急状况 一个送货员遭到袭击
Julio got a 911. A courier's been hit.
我马上到
I'm on my way.
老板 你要去哪?
Boss, where you going?
你一会还要和《时尚》杂志的女人商谈细节
The woman from Vogue is coming to talk details
关于派对的细节 你记得吗?
For the party, remember?
她之前订好的地方临时被取消
She lost her venue at the last minute.
如果我们接下这单 那么就能改变...
If we land it, it can change...
我知道 我去去就回
I know. I'll be back.
这血?
De sangre?
这家伙不远千里
This guy came all the way from miami
从迈阿密来找我们麻烦?
To fuck with us?
职业杀手 这背后黑手真聪明
Hired hitter. It's smart.
把这家伙送过来 他完成任务后
Somebody flies him up, he does the job,
回家... 不留任何线索
Then goes home... no trace.
那女孩打电话给胡里奥
The girl called Julio.
他可能还在医院
He's probably still at the hospital.
- 可能? - 还没他的最新消息
- Probably? - Haven't heard from him yet.
达里恩清理现场的时候说
When darien was cleaning up, he said
那女孩的刀伤挺严重
the girl was cut up pretty bad.
这么说她现在可能已经死了
So she could be dead by now.
我现在必须回去了
I gotta get back to the club.
我现在还有很多事没处理完
There's a lot of shit I need to be doing right now.
我们开那家店只不过是为了洗钱
We opened that place to clean our money.
你现在该做的事
The shit you need to be doing right now
是他妈的帮我想出我们下一步该怎么办
Is helping me figure out our next fucking move.
好吧 他们怎么找到她的?
Okay, how'd they find her?
或许是跟踪她吧?
Followed her, maybe?
知道该在哪 在什么时候袭击似的
They knew exactly when and where to hit.
手机 他们窃听定位了我们的手机
The phones. They got our phones.
应该不可能 我们手机都用的太空卡
I don't see how. They're all burners,
没有一个能够追踪
None of 'em traceable.
手机卧底软件 或者别的什么
Flexispy, some shit.
他们肯定用某种手段追踪我们
They gotta be tracking us some kind of way.
今晚每个人都把手机换了
Everybody rotates phones tonight.
好的 我一和胡里奥了解完情况就下达命令
Yeah, as soon as I get the all clear from Julio.
听着 一旦我们找到谁雇了这混蛋
Listen, once we figure out who hired this asshole,
我们要追根溯源
We need to mount up,
把他们一锅端了 一劳永逸
Clean up the yard once and for all.
和谁? 嗯?
With who? Hmm?
我们经营模式一向以灵巧谋略为主
Our operation's built for finesse.
现在有一帮混蛋介入我们的部分事务
We got motherfuckers that blend in, part of the scenery.
我们又没有真正的街头战士
We ain't got no real street soldiers.
我们可以征用或者雇佣一些
So we find some or buy some.
- 或者找洛沃斯帮忙 - 不
- Ask Lobos for help. - No.
如果他派人帮我们 我们就永远受他掌控
'Cause if he sends it, then he owns us forever,
如果他不派 他会乘虚而入
And if not, he takes advantage of our weakness,
把我们卖了
And he sells us out.
无论哪个 我们都死定了
Either way, we're fucked.
不过你有一件事是对的
You're right about one thing.
我们该做出回应了
We can't let this go unanswered.
真他妈对极了
That's goddamn right.
兄弟 我得回去了 真的
Look, man, I gotta get back, seriously.
唷 兄弟 你把斧头带来了?
Yo, d, you got the ax?
嘿 肖恩 进来帮帮他
Hey, shawn, get in here and help him.
他不需要插手这事
He don't need to do that.
他老爹会希望我们教他几招的
His father would want us to teach him the ropes, g.
如果他想置身事外
If he ain't gonna get his hands dirty,
他根本不必来这
He doesn't need to be here.
我能做这些
I can do it.
除非你希望我开车把你载回市中心
Unless you need me to drive you back into the city.
我自己开吧
I'll drive myself.
胡里奥一给你那女孩状况 你就电话告诉我
Call me when you hear from Julio about the girl.
工作愉快 宝贝
Have a good day at work, honey.
去你的
Fuck you.
过来 把斧子给我
Here, give me that.
嘿 看着点 肖恩
Hey. Watch this, shawn.
詹姆斯都不打电话和你说
Well, does James even bother to call and tell you
他不回来和孩子们一起吃晚饭?
He's not coming home to have dinner with the kids?
他没必要打电话
He doesn't have to call.
我知道他在哪 他在工作
I know where he is. He's working.
他在争取在夜店开一个大派对
He's trying to book a big party at the club
《时尚》杂志的派对 就在明晚
Tomorrow night for vogue magazine.
他是这么告诉你的?
That's what he told you?
是的! 如果...
Yes! And if it...
如果还有别的事情 他也会告诉我的
If it were the other business, he'd tell me that too.
我们是伴侣 妈妈
We're partners, mama.
这是婚姻
It's a marriage.
但你对这个根本不了解
But you wouldn't know too much about that.
如果他对你知无不言
Well, if he tells you everything,
那你先告诉我
You tell me why he'd open a nightclub
他为什么要开夜店
In the first place.
为了掩护 就像洗衣店
For appearances, like the laundromats.
没有杂志派对会在洗衣店开 塔莎
Ain't no magazine party at no laundromats, Tasha.
时尚模特 年轻女孩儿
High-fashion models. Young girls.
男人都难以拒绝
Hard for a man to say no to that.
幽灵对那些没胸没屁股的白人女孩没兴趣
Ghost ain't checking for no flat Ass, skinny white girl.
他有我就够了
Not when he got all this ass at home.
我以前也这么以为的 宝贝
I used to have one just like that, sugar.
告诉你 对于男人我有一件事很确定
Now, you let me tell you one thing I do know about men.
家花总不如野花香
There is always another ass.
妈妈 幽灵和我在一起很和谐
Mama, Ghost and I are fine.
只要我还供你房租
And as long as I'm paying your rent,
你说话就该小心点
You need to mind your mouth.
詹姆斯付了我的房租
James pays my rent.
别搞混了
Don't get it twisted.
如果他抛弃你 他抛弃了我们所有人
If he leaves you, he leaves all of us.
你手上的戒指什么也不是
That ring on your finger ain't no insurance.
你没办法
You can't collect alimony on income
在非法所得上讨要赡养费
The government don't know about.
感谢你过来烧饭
Thanks for coming to cook.
但你可以不来 我能搞定
But you don't need to. I'm okay.
吃吧 乖孩子
Eat, mamita.
你上次去看你爸是什么时候?
When was the last time you want to see papi?
我很久没去那了
I haven't been up there in a while.
那地方没那么好
It's not that good a place.
我们应该再去看看北边的房子
We should still go to see the one upstate again.
那里美化很好
It's pretty up there.
而且我觉得他想要水景房的想法很棒
Plus I like the idea of him being able to see the water.
我也觉得 但我和你说过
I do too, but I told you,
北边太贵
The one upstate is too expensive.
弟弟的学费我放在门边了
Junior's tuition check is by the door.
谢谢
Thank you.
我会全部还你的
You know I'll pay you back every cent.
我愿意付的
I'm happy to do it.
但是爸爸现在只能呆在那 好吗?
But papi has to stay where he is for right now, okay?
等你弟弟毕业
When junior graduates,
我们家里就没有孩子要养了
We'll have no kids left in the family.
波多黎各那里还有很多
There's plenty back in P.R.
下次你去的时候
You can bring Nadia's five boys
可以把纳迪亚的五个儿子带来
back with you next time you go.
亲爱的 你知道我说的是什么
Cute. You know what I mean.
你和... 格雷格怎么了?
What's happening with... Greg?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
别那样看着我
Don't look at me like that.
我只是觉得他不是我的真命天子
I just don't think he's the right guy.
他们都不是你的真命天子
They're never the right guy.
这个又有什么问题? 难道他不行?
What's wrong with this one? He can't fuck?
性生活不错
The sex is good.
并没有什么不好 但是...
There's nothing wrong, but...
我们之间没有了激情 没有了愉悦感
There's no goose bumps, no butterflies.
已经没有任何刺激了 你知道吗?
There's no tingling anywhere, you know?
你对待爱情还像个小女孩一样
You still think of love like you're a little girl.
愉悦感和激情只在童话中存在
Butterflies and goose bumps are fairy tales.
你永远也不会拥有
每个出现在你生活中的人 上帝自有安排
你也不想转身的时候发现一切都为时已晚
没有什么是永恒的
跟着我们 有一天你会了解自己
Stick with us. You'll get your own someday.
但是有些晚上 我会发现车尾箱里有人
But some nights, I have a body in the trunk.
以前 我和幽灵开着一辆91年的本田雅阁
Back in the day, Ghost and I drove a '91 honda accord.
你们开同一辆车?
You shared a car?
我们的后座载的女人越来越多
We got more pussy in that backseat.
那时候 卡南管着我们
Back then, Kanan kept us in line.
教我们做生意 如何做人
Taught us the business, made us men.
我和幽灵欠你父亲很多
Ghost and I owe your father big.
这就是你在这的原因
That's why you're here.
我知道
I know.
幽灵只是想你待在车上
Ghost just wants you to stay in the car
在会所的时候 看好那些漂亮的小姐
And in the club, see the pretty shit.
但是如果我们大动干戈 那就需要全员出动了
But if we go to war, it'll be all hands on deck.
我得知道你已经准备好了
I need to know you'll be ready.
我不会让你失望
I won't let you down.
很好
Good.
坎托斯
辛西娅・谢里丹来了
谢里丹女士
Ms. Sheridan.
詹姆斯・圣・帕特里克 很高兴终于见到你了
James St. Patrick. Nice to finally meet you.
你就是詹姆斯・圣・帕特里克
You're James St. Patrick.
你知道吗 我试过调查你的背景
You know, I tried to run a background check on you,
但是夜里活动的人
And no one in the nightlife world
都不太清楚你的身份
seems to know who you are.
我原以为会是个胖胖的爱尔兰人
I was expecting a fat irish guy.
我希望我符合你其他的猜想
Well, I hope I can meet your other expectations.
我也希望
I do too.
你知道我们在最后关头
You know we lost our venue
失去了我们举行这个聚会的场地
for this party at the last minute,
但我不会乱做主
But I'm not gonna make the wrong call
就因为我们已经时间紧迫
Just because we're pressed for time.
我会裁决是否满意所看到的这一切
I'll decide whether I like what I see
或者我是否应该接受我名单上的俱乐部
Or if I should keep going down my list of clubs.
我承认你这里的环境很美
I'll admit it's a beautiful space you've got here,
但是让我动容的是完美的服务
But what turns my head is perfect service.
通宵达旦
Seamless evening.
而那正是我的客户所希望的
And that is what my client expects.
但我看得出你们一直在努力工作
But I see you've been working hard.
我们确实如此 谢里丹女士
We have, Ms. Sheridan.
我们不报侥幸心理
We haven't left a single moment to chance.
那就好 因为这个聚会
That's good, because this party
不是只关系到我们在时尚杂志历史上
Isn't only about our December issue,
发行最大的十二月期刊
which is the biggest in fashion magazine history.
- 它同时也关系到我们 - 你老板的职位
- It's also about our... - Your boss's position.
你公司的编辑们都听命于她
Editors all over your building report to her.
这聚会是为了 这样说吧
This party's about, let's say,
让他们 认识到这点
making them... Feel it.
你看上去不像是会看基斯凯利的人
You don't look like you read Keith Kelly.
了解你的需求是我的分内事
I make it my business to know what you know,
谢里丹女士
Ms. Sheridan.
如果我要做好我的工作 我必须
If I'm doing my job, I should know
在你向我提要求之前知道你的需求
what you want before you ask me for it.
喂 送一两瓶波兰的伏特加去贵宾房
Hey, send a bottle or two of ultimat to V.I.P.
还有蔓越莓汁
With some cranberry juice.
我们俱乐部今晚升级了 先生
We've got a promotion tonight, sir.
我们不提供波兰的伏特加
We're not serving ultimat.
只有法国的灰雁伏特加
Just grey goose.
小姐 快给我拿我想要的东西来
Honey, you're serving whatever I want.
- 这是我的场子 - 我之前没见过你
- I own this place. - I've never seen you before.
你现在看见了?
You see me now?
是的
Yeah.
我可以偷偷为你拿些  但是我不能拿过去
I'll sneak you some ultimat, but I can't take it up there.
贵宾室不是我的工作范围
I don't work V.I.P.
你想去吗?
Do you want to?
那我的客户坐哪里?
And where does my client sit?
就在那 你可以观察到所有人的活动
Right here, where you can see all the action,
但是很少人可以看见你
But very few can see you.
她会喜欢的
She'll love it.
噢 那些摄影师应该
Oh, should the photographers
在前面那里登记还是提早来
Check in at the front or come early
加入服务?
And enter through service?
有摄影师来可不妙啊
Cameras aren't truth policy.
我们希望我们的客人
We like our guests
可以放松自己 不用考虑自己的照片
To be able to relax without thinking their images
第二天会出现在网上
Will be online the next morning.
好的 严格来说 我的人都是狗仔队
Okay, technically, my guys are paparazzi,
但他们是听话的那类 那应该没问题吧?
But they're the obedient kind. That's not a problem, right?
我的意思是 我讨厌告诉所有人我们有争执
I mean, I'd hate to tell everyone we had a conflict.
不 不 你的摄影师们可以提前来准备
No, no, your photographers can come to service early.
- 他们有充分的进入权限 - 好极了
- They'll have full access. - Excellent.
晚安 詹姆斯・圣・帕特里克
Good night, James st. Patrick.
晚安
Good night.
如果这里会有摄影师
If we're gonna have photographers here,
你应该上上镜
You should get into some of those shots.
我可不喜欢那样
Ain't my thing.
你应该在那里代表俱乐部的
You should be out there as the face of the club.
人们会想知道谁掌管这个地方
People are gonna want to know who owns this place.
斯特恩雇用我们 我们可以走向全国
Stern takes us on, we can go national.
甚至走向国际化
International, even.
越多人知道你的身份
The more people know who you are,
他们就会变得更感兴趣
The more interested he's gonna be.
你已接通联邦调查局纽约南区的
You've reached fbi special agent Greg Knox,
特工格雷格・诺克斯
Southern district of new york.
请留言
Leave a message.
喂
Hey.
这很奇怪 你总是会接电话的
That's weird. You always pick up.
如果你要来 我就在家
If you wanna come over, I'm here.
打给我
Call me.
搞什么啊...
What the fu...
汤米:
听胡里奥说那个女孩没死
换部手机
抱歉我来迟了
Uh, sorry I'm late.
咖啡难闻死了 所以我冲了一壶新的
Coffee smelled like dick, so I had to make a new pot.
噢 很抱歉 拉瓦罗女士
Oh, hey, sorry, Ms. Lavarro.
我无意冒犯 萨克斯先生
I'm not offended, Mr. Saxe.
那味道也让我很难受
The smell of dick turns me off too.
说到迟到 你在外面看见诺克斯特工了吗?
Speaking of late, you see agent Knox out there?
- 他应该在这的 - 没有
- He should be here. - No.
我绘制了现有在五个区的
I've charted the existing distribution networks
分布网络
In the five boroughs.
- 我想构建一个清晰的... - 安吉拉
- I'd like to construct a clear... - Angela,
我觉得我们应该多讨论一下鲁伊斯
I was thinking we should talk more about Ruiz.
洛沃斯转移了对鲁伊斯的注意力
Lobos moved on from Ruiz,
我们也该如此
so we should too.
那已经是个死胡同了
He's a dead end.
谢谢 早安
Thank you. Morning.
- 早安 - 早安 先生
- Morning. - Good morning, sir.
我觉得我得看看
Thought I'd see how
你们费利佩・洛沃斯专案组进展如何
Your Felipe Lobos task force is coming along.
我们收到联邦部队的电报
We got a wire from the federales.
洛沃斯昨晚在华瑞兹市着陆
Lobos landed in Juarez last night.
他现在呆在边界附近 所以我们现在在竞赛
He's staying close to the border, so now we're racing
吉利福利亚州和德克萨斯州南部地区
both california and texas southern districts
都力争起诉
to get an indictment.
我们都意识到紧迫性 先生
We're all aware of the urgency, sir.
事实上 安吉拉才刚加入
In fact, Angela was just diving in.
我们在创建一个概要来协助找出
We're creating a profile to help identify
- 洛沃斯在纽约的经销商 - 确切地说
- Lobos's new york distro. - More specifically,
我们在讨论
We were discussing a meeting Lobos had
洛沃斯和索尔达多族的比沃拉・鲁伊斯的会面
With Vibora Ruiz from .
正如我们讨论的 洛沃斯告诉鲁伊斯
And as discussed, Lobos told Ruiz
索尔达多对他来说太低档了
The soldados were too low-rent for him,
他们没有达成协议
They made no agreement,
所以那并不是个优渥的地区
so it's not a fertile area.
但洛沃斯如何安排位置呢?
But how did Lobos arrange that sit?
把鲁伊斯拿下
Down with Ruiz.
我发了通缉令逮捕鲁伊斯的助理
I issued a warrant for a Ruiz lieutenant,
诺马・阿奇斯罗
Nomar Arcielo...
你发了通缉令? 用什么合理的理由?
You issued the warrant? With what probable cause?
纽约警察追踪到诺马的一部太空卡电话
A burner cell traced to Nomar by NYPD
在洛沃斯的会晤时间段
spiked high usage details around the time
使用频率攀升
of the Lobos meeting.
如果是他安排的话 他可能有有用信息
If he set it up, he could have valuable information.
我和这个有过紧密法官合作
I've worked closely with this judge.
如果我们太过火了 他会制止的
He'll slap us down if we overreach.
这就是为什么所有申请都要经过我
That's why all applications go across my desk.
明白 我只是想先发制人而已
Understood. I was trying to be proactive.
正如你说的 先生
You know, since, like you said, sir,
其他办事处也在着手洛沃斯的案子
Other offices are on Lobos too.
鲁伊斯是我们的本土优势
Ruiz is our local advantage.
以后 跟团队一起工作
In future, work with the team.
当我们都可以
Cops and robbers is more fun when we all can play.
也许我们可以得到些新的信息
In case we could get something new,
调用个特工来执行你的令状
Call an agent to serve your warrant.
- 现在继续... - 其实
- Now, moving on... - actually,
特工格雷格・诺克斯正在确定诺马的位置
Special agent Greg Knox is trying to locate Nomar
正如我们所说 我昨晚给他打电话了
As we speak. I called him last night.
很好
Great.
现在 像我刚说的 我们知道洛沃斯正想
Now, as I was saying, we know Lobos wants
找一条可靠的运货途径
a reliable pathway for his product.
最有可能的进货点就是新泽西的伊丽莎白港
The most likely point of entry is port Elizabeth, New Jersey,
所以我们要找的批发商
So the distributor we're looking for
应该有广泛的关系网...
Should have an extensive network...
谢谢 宝贝儿
Thanks, babe.
对不起我那天晚上提前走了
I'm sorry I left early the other night.
我不想打扰你 你正和别的人在一起呢
I didn't want to bother you. You were with somebody.
看样子你很想和她聊聊啊
Looked like you really wanted to talk to her.
我那天好像是碰见了一个高中时的朋友
I ran into a friend from high school that night, I think.
我记不清了
I can't remember.
嘿
Hey.
没什么可烦的 小T
Ain't no reason to trip, T.
对不起 昨天和我妈聊天来着
Sorry. Mama and I were talking yesterday,
我只是有点...
And I just...
别介意
Never mind.
圣帕特里克夫人 嗨
Mrs. St. Patrick, hey.
我来点咖啡您不介意吧
I hope it's okay I took some coffee.
你随意啊
Help yourself.
你在哪长大的 肖恩?
Where'd you grow up, Shawn?
霍利斯 土生土长
Hollis, originally.
- 卡多佐 - 不是吧 我去过卡多佐
- Cardozo - No way. I went to Cardozo.
喔 霍利斯一定变了
Pssh, yo, hollis must have changed,
因为我那时候可没见过路边有你这样的女生
'cause I ain't never seen no girls like you round the way.
那有许多像我一样的女生
There's plenty of girls just like me out there
想找一个像你一样负责的男生
Looking for somebody responsible like you
好好对她们
to treat 'em right.
你有女朋友了吧?
You have a girlfriend now?
等一下
Wait.
我好像不该问你这事
I probably shouldn't ask you that.
不 不 不 没关系你问吧
No, no, no, it's cool that you asked.
我没女朋友
I ain't seeing nobody.
你单身?
You're single?
我不信
I don't believe it.
你想让我跟你约会
You wanted me to see you.
那天晚上在车里
The other night in the car.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
昨晚汤米跟你说了吧?
Talk to Tommy last night?
- 全新的 - 你们都要换手机?
- Brand-new. - Y'all had to rotate the phones
出什么事了?
What happened?
没什么 只是未雨绸缪
Nothing. Just taking precautions.
这紧身裤让你撑得真够劲啊 小妞
You giving that spandex a workout of its own, girl, huh?
晚上见
I'll see you tonight.
- 好吧 - 行了
- All right. - Okay.
哦 等一下... 幽灵 你新换的手机号!
Oh, wait... Ghost, your new number!
我他妈现在怎么管你啊?
How the fuck am I supposed to get ahold of you now?
柯林斯一进来 萨克斯就出去了
Collins walks in, and Saxe busts out
说什么"我们还没弄完鲁伊斯的事"
With this "we're not done with Ruiz" bullshit.
结果你已经开始找这个叫诺马的了
Turns out you're already looking for this Nomar guy,
我当众丢了脸
And I'm caught with my pants down.
你应该告诉我啊
You should have called me.
萨克斯特意让我不这么做
Saxe gave me explicit instructions not to do so.
好吧 去他的 也去你的
Okay, fuck him. But fuck you too.
是有命令
There's a chain of command.
你知道他跟我过不去
You knew he was fucking with me.
我该做什么?
What should I have done?
我做什么之前都让你知道
I call you to check in before every move,
我们之间的事情也很清楚
and it's pretty clear what's going on between us.
对不对?
Am I right?
是你说我们的关系要保密的
You said we had to keep our relationship a secret.
要是规则变了 告诉我
If the rules have changed, let me know.
规则没变
The rules haven't changed.
别人要是发现了
People find out,
会夸你"好样的"还会跟你击掌
you'll get "attaboys" and high fives,
而我就会因为和一个特工上了床名誉扫地
While I'll lose all credibility for fucking an agent.
我不想把事公开
I don't want to go public.
我就是不想让你糊弄我
I just don't want you to sandbag me.
我没糊弄你 我遵守了规定
I didn't sandbag you. I followed protocol.
咱俩的规则也算数
Those rules matter too.
祝你早日找到你那人 诺克斯特工
Good luck finding your man, agent Knox.
安吉拉 咱还没说清楚呢
Angela, we're not done here.
拜拜 格雷格
Goodbye, Greg.
这也太搞笑了
This is ridiculous.
对不起 您所拨打的号码
We're sorry, the number you have reached
不在服务区
is not in service.
请检查您的号码或稍后再拨...
Please check the number or try your call...
不好意思 詹姆斯在吗?
Excuse me. Is James here?
在
Yeah.
看见老板了吗?
Got eyes on the boss?
安琪
Angie.
杰米!
Jamie!
对不起我打扰了你工作
Sorry I had to track you down at work.
你换电话啦?
You changed your cell?
我得把我手机扔了
I had to ditch my phone.
夜店生意 你懂得
Nightclub business, you know.
太多人知道你的号 就很麻烦
Too many people get your number, it gets messy.
我很开心你还真打了
I'm glad you actually called.
这地方白天真不一样
This place looks so different during the day.
你是说看起来像破产了吗?
You're saying it looks busted now?
有点
A little.
不 其实我只是惊讶于
No, I'm just surprised at how, at night,
它在晚上的变化
It's transformed.
这就是初衷
That's the idea.
人们晚上来这可以随心所欲地
People come here and become whoever they wanna be
转换自己的身份
for the night.
这是一种幻想
It's a fantasy.
然后他们就会买好多酒
And then they buy a lot of drinks.
对
Yes.
你还没告诉我你是怎么建立起这一切呢
You still haven't told me how you made this happen.
我们清理了一片废旧的场地
We cleaned up an abandoned lot,
用来做停车场收费
Charged for parking.
用那钱买了一个自助洗衣店
That money bought a laundromat,
之后买了一个又一个
Then another and another.
我心底一直记着我父亲的夜店
I always had my father's place in the back of my mind,
然后我们发现了这个地方 之后...
And then we found this space, and...
汤米觉得我疯了
Tommy thought I was crazy.
等一下 汤米? 汤米・伊根?
Wait, Tommy? Tommy Egan?
你还跟他在一块?
You still hang out with him?
他是我夜店的合作伙伴
He's my partner in the club.
怎么 你惊讶我俩铁到现在?
What, you surprised we still tight?
说老实话 是的
Yeah, to be honest.
我一直觉得汤米太像街头混混了
I always thought Tommy liked the streets too much.
你一定给了他很多积极影响
You must have been a good influence on him.
我来给你看点东西
Let me show you something.
小心脚下
Watch your step.
你是当真呢吗?
Are you serious?
我不知道现在还有人弄这个!
I didn't know people still made these!
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
闭上眼睛 安琪
Close your eyes, Angie.
闭上了
They're closed.
这还是你最喜欢的歌吗?
This still your favorite song?
你逗我呢?
Are you kidding me?
依然让我想在摄像机前
Makes me wanna break out the baseball jersey
脱了棒球服和护膝
and the kneepads from the video.
那么接下来会怎样呢?
So what happens next?
我知道你有个计划
I know you got a plan.
要是一切顺利 那我们就开分店
If truth takes off, then we open a second club
就在纽约这
Right here in new york city.
之后没准在迈阿密或者拉斯维加斯
Then maybe one in miami or vegas.
这得干上一阵子 但是我...
It's gonna take a while, but I...
一定会做到的
You'll get there.
你都走到这了
You got here.
你今天晚上要来看看吗?
You wanna come through tonight?
我们要给时尚杂志开狂欢派对
We got a big party for vogue magazine.
哇 真了不起
Wow, that's huge.
我很想来 但我要工作
I wish I could. I gotta work.
我希望你的客户会为你这种牺牲多付你钱
I hope your clients pay extra for that kind of dedication.
- 真该死 - 不是那种工作
- Damn. - It's not that kind of law.
我给政府工作 它...
I work for the government. It's...
很无聊
Boring.
无论如何
Anyway, you're gonna be too busy tonight
你今晚也会忙到没法陪我
to hang out with me.
我会想办法
I'll make the time.
来吧 安琪
Come on, Angie.
好吧 我会来看看
Okay, I'll come through.
真的?
Yeah?
冲 冲 冲 冲 冲
Go, go, go, go, go.
快点 汤米叔叔!
Oh, come on, uncle Tommy!
你本该罩着我的
You're supposed to have my back.
这是加速模式还是什么?
Is this some sped-up mode or something?
我不记得它这么快啊
I don't remember it being this fast.
不 只是你老了
No, you're just old.
只是等会儿...什么?
Just wait... what?
- 你老了! - 什么?
- You're old! - What?
该我了
I got next.
什么事 老爹?
Oh, what's up, dad?
你说什么事 儿子?
What's up, son?
- 去做你的作业去 - 好吧
- Go finish your homework. - All right.
- 我知道你没做完 - 快去吧
- I know you didn't finish it. - Get outta here.
我是怎么跟你说玩游戏这件事的 嗯?
And what'd I tell you about playing those games, huh?
你想除掉被割伤的那个妹子
The girl who got cut, you want clipped.
- 我别无他法 - 我不明白
- I don't see another way. - I don't know, man.
就像你说的那样 她守了规矩
Like you said, she followed protocol.
打给了胡里奥
She called Julio.
就算是救她自己命 她也没打911报警
She didn't call 911, even to save her own life.
她身上有毒品 打911报警的话
she calls 911 with the drugs on her,
就得进去了 她当时很冷静
She's going to jail. She kept a cool head.
汤米 你跟我还好好的 就是因为她没搞砸
You and I are good, tommy, because she didn't fuck it up.
别的手下会怎么说这事
What does it say to other soldiers
她做的很好 我们还是把她除掉了?
If she does her job well and we ice her anyway?
干得好!
Nice kill!
说实话
The truth.
就像你想要的那样 他们是可以被替代的
They're replaceable, just like you wanted it.
她也是如此
She's replaceable.
我们现在讨论的是个女人 幽灵
This is a female we're talking about, Ghost.
现在谁还会要她
Who's gonna want her now?
某天她醒过来
One day she's gonna wake up,
看着她残破的脸
look at her ruined fucking face
和她那残破的人生 她就会要我们对她负责
And her ruined fucking life, and she's gonna blame us for it.
就算她不认识我们 她知道胡里奥
And even though she doesn't know us, she knows Julio.
她知道我们整个运作模式
She knows how our whole thing works.
她就会说 "去他妈的这些蛋逼
She's gonna be like, "fuck these motherfuckers.
我要去报警"
I'm going to the cops."
指望这些一天一个花样的送货女?
Over some random-ass courier chick?
你想冒这个险?
That's a risk you wanna take?
我会跟胡里奥说的
I'll talk to Julio.
嘿 小T 准备好了没?
Yo, t, you ready to go?
我们预订的还有20分钟就到了
Our reservation's in 20 minutes.
快了
Almost.
祝你好运
Peace.
没有 我们很好 没问题
Nah, man, we're good. No problems.
好的 就那样解决
Good. Let's keep it that way.
把那女的样子告诉我们的人
Remind our people of the bitch's description
以防她回来
In case she comes back.
那个送货员怎么说? 那双怪鞋?
What did the courier say? Fucking weird shoes?
是的 她穿了双亮粉色运动鞋
Yeah, she had bright pink sneakers on.
我已经告诉他们了
I told them already.
好的
All right, good.
我还是小心点好
Better be on my toes.
那些人瞄着你想要
One of these motherfuckers staring might try
把你带回家呢
to take you home.
真希望我对你来说也有这样的魅力
Wish I had that effect on you.
你想说什么?
What's that supposed to mean?
我只是说 如果我那样的话
I'm just saying, if I'm all that,
你会多回回家的
You'd be home more.
我不回家是因为要工作 想给你和孩子
I'm not home because I'm working, trying to provide
创造更好的条件
For you and the kids.
得供你的吃穿各方面
Paying for that weave and that dress and those shoes.
不用你来给我施压 好么?
I don't need you stressing me, all right?
我没要给你施压
I ain't trying to stress you.
但我都还没你的新手机号
But I ain't even got your new digits,
而我是你妻子
And I'm your wife.
现在你有我
Now you got me
和司机的号码了
and the driver.
你说的对 宝贝
You're right, baby.
是我的错 我给忘了
My bad. I forgot.
你最近可把我撂一边去了
You've been forgetting me a lot lately.
拜托 我知道你不会拒绝
Come on, I know you're not turning down
宫保鸡丁的
Kung pao chicken.
我还特地按你喜欢 多加了花生
I even got the extra peanuts, just how you like it.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
但不表示我气已经消了
That doesn't mean I'm not still mad.
你知道我别无选择
You know I didn't have a choice.
你又不肯认输
You just don't like to lose.
你想什么时候告诉我发生什么事了 幽灵?
When you gonna tell me what's going on, Ghost?
我又不是孩子
I ain't no kid.
新手机和行头?
New phones and shit?
你们不会出车祸了吧?
Guessing y'all had a car accident?
我们开出路面了
We got run off the road.
你的车还能开么?
Your car still running?
还行 但维修费用可能
Still running, but the repairs might be
太贵了付不起
too expensive to make.
另外一个人的车呢?
And the other guy's car?
彻底废了
Totaled.
我们得把它拖走了
We had to tow it.
现在
So now,
该说说下一步计划了
It's about the next move.
把它拖去拆车厂了?
You take it to the chop shop?
还有部分在么?
Still got the parts?
你在想什么?
What you thinking?
过去的时候
Back in the day,
还记得那些多米尼加的孩子怎么对
remember what those dominican boys did
那辆红色卡车的么?
to that red truck?
一半开去一个车库
Half went to one garage,
一半开去了另一个
Half to another.
别说那些扯淡的话了
Stopped all that bullshit.
还要酒么 夫人?
More wine, ma'am?
好的
Yes, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
听着
Look.
萨克斯跟我说如果跟踪阿奇斯罗
Saxe told me that if nothing came from going
毫无收获的话 没有人会知道的
After arcielo, no one would even know about it.
没想到他会蠢到在不知道
I didn't think he was stupid enough to go off about it
我有没有抓到人之前就泄露风声
without knowing if I'd catch the guy.
请告诉我萨克斯浪费了纳税人的钱
Please tell me Saxe wasted taxpayer dollars
让你去抓个行踪不定的人
sending you on a wild-goose chase,
然后那家伙离开了城里
and the guy's left town.
你抓到他了
You got him.
我他妈是个联邦调查局特工 安吉拉
I'm a fucking FBI agent, Angela.
当然抓到他了
Damn right I got him.
他还带着他那该死的手机
He still had his goddamn phone.
确凿证据表明他开了那个会或知道是谁开的
Conclusive proof he set the meeting or knows who did.
萨克斯赢了
Saxe wins.
对大家来讲是好消息 对我不是
Good news for the team, bad news for me.
或许不是呢
Maybe not.
直到你听到他还打给谁了
Wait till you hear who else he called.
伊莎贝尔・鲁伊斯
Isabel Ruiz.
比沃拉・鲁伊斯的女儿?
Vibora Ruiz's daughter?
她不是才十四岁么?
Isn't she 14?
诺马打给她的?
Nomar called her?
连续几个礼拜一周打好几次
Multiple times a week for weeks.
这不可能
No fucking way.
那个受伤的手下是个女的
The soldier that got hurt's a woman.
脸被割花了 汤米认为她会说出去
Face all cut up. Tommy thinks she'll talk.
但她尽管在生命危急时刻还是显得很忠诚
But she was loyal when her life was at stake.
你想要女人的忠诚? 给她安全感
You want a woman's loyalty? Give her security.
给了她安全感
You give her that,
她就再也不会背叛你
She'll never betray you.
宝贝 拜托
Baby, come on.
他很识趣的
He knows better than to watch.
而且萨克斯不知道这些?
And Saxe doesn't know about this?
我没告诉他 我在跟你说
I didn't tell him. I'm telling you.
所以我们和好了?
So are we good?
和好了
We're good.
妈妈带孩子们去看电影了
Mama took the kids to the movies.
我们大概有一个小时
We got an hour, maybe.
当我们谈正经事的时候...
When we talk business...
就像初次见面一样
It's like when we first met.
就像邦妮可克莱德
Like bonnie and clyde.
什么?
What?
- 没什么 - 拜托
- Nothing. - Come on.
用力点
Harder.
- 你确定? - 用力点
- You sure? - Harder.
你确定现在要去楼下的酒吧?
You sure you gotta go down to the club right now?
是的
Yeah.
我得走了
I gotta go.
邦妮
Bonnie.
今晚期待你们好好表现
I'm expecting perfection from you tonight.
来俱乐部参加聚会的人们
The people who are coming to the club for this party...
模特 杂志编辑 演员 富豪们
Models, magazine editors, actors, rich motherfuckers
可都不是好打发的主
Who ain't do nothing to earn that shit.
但他们有好朋友
But they have the right friends.
他们在这里过得很愉快 所以他们回来了
They have a good time here, they come back.
带来了更多的人
They bring more people.
事实是 有越来越多的人听说我们的店
Truth is, the more people hear about the spot,
我们就会富有
We all get rich.
我不会给你们联营小费
I don't make you pool tips.
我不相信那套
I don't believe in that shit.
那样只会养出些懒汉
Then the lazy motherfuckers win.
但是我们今晚需要合作
But tonight we work as a team.
让彼此都进入角色 让这里热力四射
Keep each other on point, make it hot,
满足他们一切要求 伙计们...
Give 'em what they want. Fellas...
如果有基佬想要你的电话号码 就给他
If a cat's gay and he wants your number, give it to him.
姑娘们 你们已经知道该怎么做了
Ladies... shit, you already know what to do.
你们都已经很熟练了
You've been doing it your whole lives.
今晚我们的客人是别人请来的
Tonight our guests are drinking on someone else's dime.
要保证他们还会来 而且是自己掏腰包
Make 'em want to come back and spend their own money.
- 老板 该营业了 - 表演时间到
- Time to open the doors, boss. - Showtime.
保证没有人出来
No one else comes out.
你有没有那些来客的名单?
You keeping track of the arrivals?
我想看一下叫安吉拉・巴尔德斯的客人
I want to know about an angela valdes.
目前还这位客人还没来
No one with that name has checked in yet.
不过辛西娅已经到VIP包间了
Cynthia's up in v.I.P., though.
她在找你
She's looking for you.
告诉布埃索 他仍然要他妈的去送货
Tell Bueso he's still gotta do the damn deliveries.
他拿到他的枪了 对吗?
He's got his fucking piece, right?
你所拨打的电347...
You've reached 347...
在玩我吗 混蛋?
Are you kidding me, motherfucker?
我必须得承认 我被了惊到了
Hey, I have to admit I'm impressed.
詹姆斯 你把这里经营的很好
You run a smooth operation here, James.
- 嗯 - 连我老板都说
- Mm. - Even my boss said
她喜欢这的食物... 虽然她一点都不吃
she liked the food... not that she ate any.
你知道 我不只是给《时尚》办派对的
You know, I don't just plan parties for Vogue.
我还打理GQ 魅力 美食赏鉴会 社交宴会
I handle GQ, allure, bon appetit, vanity fair.
这些活动全年无休
It's events all year long.
而且要为我的非康泰纳仕集团的客户服务
Plus servicing my non Conde nast clients.
这可责任重大
It's a lot of responsibility.
你知道 我在想我们俩
You know, I was thinking that you and I
应该长期合作
should work together long-term.
我让你上知名的报纸
You know, I bring you the press, the big names.
你给我大折扣
You give me a big, fat discount.
怎么样?
How does that sound?
成交
Deal.
哦 你知道吗? 我要确认
Oh, you know what? I will make sure
这张照片会登出来
This runs in the post.
把你的脸露出来 让这里名声远扬
Get your face out there. Make this place a brand name.
- 怎么啦 伙计? - 嗨 汤米
- What's up, man? - Hey, tommy.
哦 不好意思 我们正要照相
Oh, sorry, we're just about to take a picture,
你若能等 你一会就可以和詹姆斯讲话了
So if you can wait a minute, you can talk to James in a sec.
哦 不 我认为詹姆斯现在就想和我谈谈
Oh, no, I think James wants to talk to me right now.
辛西娅 我一会就回来 工作太多了
Cynthia, I'll be right back. Work never stops.
玩的开心
Enjoy the party.
你他妈的在想什么 伙计?
What the fuck you thinking, man?
你想上明天的报纸吗?
You wanna be in the paper tomorrow?
你想所有人都知道你是谁 对吗 幽灵?
You want everyone to know who you are, Ghost?
好吧 伙计 不照相了
All right, man. No pictures.
我得回去了 我们一会儿再说
I gotta get back. We'll talk about it later.
不 我们现在就得说清楚
No, we'll talk about this right now.
我们和他们不一样 幽灵
We're not like these people, Ghost.
我们上报纸了并不是件好事
You and me in the paper ain't a good thing.
如果我们上报纸了 代表着我们被捕了
You and me in the paper means we got got.
那些人不知道我们的事儿 伙计
These people don't know about our other thing, man.
- 一张照片而已... - 已经够多了!
- One picture... - Is too many!
在照片上 你站在这些人的后面
You standing next to these people in pictures
人们的下一个问题就是 这个混蛋是谁?
The next question is, who the fuck is this guy?
然后窥探你的生活
People digging in your life story,
你猜他们会发现什么?
What do you think they're gonna find?
我们要低调 只在必要时出现
We lay low. We sell what we need to sell.
只杀必杀之人
We ice who we need to ice.
所有都是为了生意 一直都是
All business, all the time.
这就是为了生意!
This is about business!
自从我们开了这家店 你就不再关心生意了
You ain't been about business since we opened this place.
看看你的电话 混蛋
Check your phone, motherfucker.
- 怎么了? - 今晚有个婊子
- What happened? - Same bitch tried
想要干掉布埃索
To jump Bueso tonight.
他逃走了
He got away.
- 他一定带电话了 - 没有
- Must have kept his phone. - No.
他有自己的安排
He kept his route.
那些混蛋知道我们的流程
These fuckers know our system.
他们知道我们的安排
They know our routine.
你想怎么办?
What you wanna do?
没空想了 伙计
No time for thinking, man.
你他妈到底想干嘛?
What the fuck you wanna do?
今晚塔莎说了些关于多米尼加人的事儿
Tasha said something tonight about the dominicans.
还记得 他们对迪罗干的事儿吗?
What they did with d-lo, remember that?
不是什么好事儿
That was some sick shit.
我们为什么不更进一步?
Why don't we take that to the next level?
让所有人知道 我们不怕干下流的勾当?
Show everybody we ain't afraid to do dirt?
如果我们办的好 就能让那些混蛋离我们远点
We do it right, it'll shut this shit down for good.
那要是没办的不好呢?
And if it doesn't?
那我们就要准备一场硬仗
Then we go to war.
那是 诺马・阿奇斯罗吗?
Is that Nomar arcielo?
是的 先生
Yes, sir, agent knox brought him in
诺克斯特工昨晚带他来审问
for questioning last night.
我不敢相信 你还用这个号码 诺马
I can't believe you kept the phone, Nomar.
简直蠢透了
That was incredibly stupid.
你又不能证明这是我的
You can't prove it's mine.
八个人住在哪里
Eight people live in that place.
而且你了解我们拉丁人的
Plus, you know us Latinos.
我们的表亲很多
We got a lot of cousins.
这个可能是任何人的
Could belong to any of us.
我们知道这是你的
We know it's yours.
比沃拉・鲁伊斯让你安排
Vibora Ruiz had you arrange his meeting
他和费利佩・洛沃斯会面
with felipe Lobos.
没错 诺马 这就是你在这的原因
Yes, Nomar, that's why you're here.
我们不想抓你 我们也不想抓你的老板
We don't want you. We don't even want your boss.
我们只想抓到洛沃斯
We want Lobos.
这张就是这个号码
This is a list of all the numbers
所有的通话记录
dialed and received by that phone.
你的号码
Your phone.
就告诉我那些号码是洛沃斯的 或者他手下的
Just tell me which numbers belong to Lobos or his men.
你想让我告发费利佩・洛沃斯?
You want me to rat on felipe Lobos?
我还想多活几天呢?
I rather live a couple more days.
只几天吗 多活几年不好吗?
Days. How about years?
我可以让你在莱文沃斯吃点苦头
I can have you doing hard time in Leavenworth
周末以前 每天被干
By the end of the week, getting fucked every day.
如果够幸运 每周还能见一小时阳光
An hour of sunlight, if you're lucky.
我被关在那里过
I been inside already.
那时我才十九岁 太弱小 根本打不过他们
I was 19 and weak, too small to fight them off.
你得习惯被折磨
You get used to getting fucked.
让你懂得感谢女人
Makes you appreciate a woman.
我现在可是个战士
I'm a soldado now.
我的内心比身体更强大
I'm more powerful inside than I am out here.
看来这个审讯会比他预想的要长
This is gonna take a little longer than he thought.
为什么不让我试试?
Why don't I give it a try?
请让我们单独谈谈 好吗?
Can I have the room, please?
我觉得这主意可不怎么样 特工
I don't think that's a good idea, agent.
他是我的嫌疑人
This is my suspect.
如果我需要你 会叫你的
I'll call you if I need you.
我要让你菊花残
他们在圣胡安都可以听到你呻吟声
前提是我没把你的菊花搞残
我查了你所有的拨出电话
I ran the numbers of the outgoing calls you made.
大部分是太空卡
Mostly other burner cells.
有些可能是墨西哥人
Other soldados, probably.
还有号码可能和洛沃斯有关系
And the numbers that might be Lobos-related.
但是你打的电话中有一个
But one of the numbers you called
是注册的
is actually registered.
你知道是哪一个吗?
You know which one?
不知道
No.
你不让鲁伊斯知道的小秘密
Your little secret you're hiding from Ruiz.
你曾给他十四岁的女儿 伊莎贝尔打过电话
You've been calling isabel, his 14-year-old daughter.
她怎么会知道这些?
How could she know that?
我初步调查报告上写了这个号码
The numbers were in my initial report,
你用来申请逮捕令的证据
The evidence you used to get the warrant.
你没有和鲁伊斯的档案做过比对吗?
You didn't cross-check them with the Ruiz file?
我猜她做了
I guess she did.
就像我和那个白痴说的一样
Like I told el blanco,
这手机可能是任何人的
The phone could've been used by anybody.
说不定是我表弟在学校遇到了她
Maybe my cousin met her at school.
有可能 不过你觉得鲁伊斯会相信谁
Could be, but who do you think Ruiz is going to believe,
你 还是我?
You or me?
尤其是我给他看这里这个之后
Especially after I show him this.
胡说 这他妈是伪造的
That's bullshit. That's a fucking fake!
你觉得他会相信谁?
不 比沃拉・我没给你女儿打过电话
我不知道警察们哪在弄到的她私处的相片
伙计
Chacho...
一旦鲁伊斯发现这事
你就无处可藏了
而且他还会让所有索尔达多族人知道
And when he lets the soldado nation know
你喜欢乱搞小女孩...
You like to mess with little girls...
到时我们到要看看
then we'll see
你到底需要习惯被怎么折磨
what you get used to.
或者把你所知的
Or you can tell me
跟洛沃斯有关的所有事都告诉我
everything you know about Lobos,
那么你是恋童癖的事
And your nasty pedophile bullshit
就只是我们之间的小秘密...
Will stay our little secret..
去你妈的 你个背信弃义的婊子
去你妈的 混账东西
签一下协议
Just sign the agreement
这里还有这里
Here and here.
不错
Not bad.
该死的?
What the fuck?
无论谁干涉我们要知道他们老板是谁
Whoever's fucking with us knows who they hired.
他们要一清二楚地收到消息
They'll get the message loud and clear.
在街上散布两天的消息 人们就会知道
Two days of street chatter and people will know
我们可不是好惹的
We're not the ones to fuck with.
那个女孩?
And about the girl?
马上打电话给J
Calling J now.
- 胡里奥 - 是我
- Julio. - Yeah.
伙计 买些花 你要去医院
Get some flowers, man. You're going to the hospital.
1804号房在哪?
Where is room 1804?
先生 那边
That way, sir.
你来这里做什么?
他们派我来的
可以看一下你的身份证吗?
Can I see your I.D.?
我是她男朋友
听着
我们不能再在一起了
你是要跟我分手吗?
我不明白
现在起你的脸很容易辨识度很高
很容易认出来
我跟医生谈过了
恢复不到以前的容貌了
你不能再给我们送货了
那么现在怎么办?
审讯室里干得好
Nice work in there.
诺马真的在他手机留下
Did Nomar really leave that picture
女孩的照片?
of the girl on his phone?
我从一宗儿童色情案找到的
I grabbed it from a child porn case.
根本不是伊莎贝尔
It's not even isabel.
厉害
Good girl.
你好?
Hello?
看来现在打给你不太合适宜
You ain't seen fit to call to say
昨晚你没来?
You weren't coming through last night?
- 杰米? - 放我鸽子
- Jamie? - Stand a brother up
还装作听不出我的声音......好吧
and pretend not to know his voice... okay.
我对昨晚的事道歉
I'm sorry about last night.
要开个工作会议
A work meeting came up.
我只想看看你还好吗
I just wanted to make sure you're all right.
我补偿你怎么样?
How about I make it up to you?
他一个小时之前走了
He left about half an hour ago.
我想让他带我去吃午餐
I wanted him to take me to lunch.
他有说他什么时候回来吗?
Did he say when he'd be back?
没有
No.
可他从来没说过
But he never does.
你想让我给他打个电话?
You want me to give him a call?
不 我来打
No, I'll do it.
你出去一下
I don't need an audience.
圣帕特里克太太
Mrs. St. Patrick.
嘿 你好吗?
Hey, are you okay?
我找不到幽灵 我有点担心了
I can't reach Ghost, and I'm starting to get worried.
我看着圣帕特里克先生
I've got eyes on mr. St. Patrick,
他很好
And he's just fine.
好吧
Okay.
我感觉好点了
Guess I feel better, then.
肖恩 你可以帮我个忙吗?
Shawn, could you do me a favor?
别告诉幽灵 我打过电话找他
Don't tell Ghost I called.
他不喜欢我查他岗
He wouldn't like me checking up on him.
可以是我们的小秘密吧?
Can it be our little secret?
是的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
我们的小秘密
Our little secret.
谢谢你拿它来报答我 大富豪
Thanks for making it up to me, big spender.
想改变一下线路吗?
You want the change?
我可不想都是在一个地方度过
Promise not to spend it all in one place.
哇
Wow.
好久没来这了
Haven't been here in years.
那时候我最喜欢就是野外旅行了
This was my favorite field trip back in the day.
他们总是按字母顺序安排我们在车上的位置
They always put us on the bus in alphabetical order, man.
我必须得调整整个顺序就为了坐在你旁边
I had to work up a whole scheme just to sit next to you.
约瑟・乌里韦总是想要我所有午饭钱
Jose Uribe always wanted all my lunch money.
所以你都没吃? 真的吗?
So you didn't eat? Seriously?
这么做值得啊
It was worth it.
来吧
Come on.
让我们进去看看鲸鱼
Let's go inside, see the whale.
好
Okay.
以前站在这下面让我感到自己很渺小
Used to make me feel so small standing under here.
当我渐渐长大
thought I'd feel different
我想感受会不同
when I got older.
我猜有些事情不会变
I guess some things don't change.
我想这次我们不会
Well, I don't think we'll get busted kissing
在楼梯间里激吻了
in the stairwell this time.
我们被逮到时我觉得很尴尬
I was so embarrassed we got caught.
我不觉得
I wasn't.
我给你看看一些东西
I got you something
当你去拿地图时
When you went to get the map.
我给我们俩各拿了一个
One for each of us.
你挑战我 说你不会从礼品店偷任何东西
You dared me I wouldn't boost anything from the gift shop.
我食言了 是吧?
Yeah, I ate those words, didn't I?
这次我是买的
I bought 'em this time.
这真好 谢谢
This is great. Thank you.
看 安琪 我情不自禁
Look, angie, I can't stop
去想肯定有你下次来
Thinking there must... must be a reason you came
俱乐部的理由
In the club the other night.
一个理由就是我们在这次之后
A reason we're seeing each other again
又见面
After all this time.
我围绕在你身边...
Me being around you...
跟你在一起...
Me being with you...
感觉很好
It just feels right.
我懂的
I know.
我也是
Me too.
噢 天啊
Oh, fuck.
我电话没响
My phone didn't ring.
我要走了 马上
I gotta go, like, right now.
杰米 对不起
Jamie, I'm sorry.
再见
Bye.
- 幽灵打给你? - 是的
- Ghost call you? - Yeah.
都没看到机器爆炸 你是怎么做的?
How'd you do it without setting off the machines?
医院很机警
Hospitals are tricky.
做什么?
Do what?
老板让我告诉她给她升职了
Boss told me to tell her she was promoted.
她要和马库斯在银行工作了
She's gonna start working with Marcus in the bank.
他没告诉我了结了这妹子
Yo, he didn't tell me to ice the chick.
我领会错了吗?
Did I get it wrong?
没有
Nope.
你准备好那些存款单了?
You ready with those deposit slips?
我不喜欢这么做事
I don't like doing things this way.
可你要再多保住一天你的工作
But you get to keep your job for one more day.
开玩笑呢 伙计
It's a joke, man.
别生气
Lighten up.
詹姆斯在哪?
Where's James?
他在后面
He's in the back.
我叫他吗?
Should I get him?
不用了
Nope.
不好意思 我刚出去透透气
I am so sorry. I just stepped out for some air.
你今天赢得柯林斯很好的印象
You scored major points with collins today.
你彻底被他看中了
You're on his radar in a big way.
他想让你下周末去和他打牌
He wants you to come to his poker night next weekend.
霍尔德可能在那里 他会到城里来
Holder might be there. He'll be in town.
天啊
Holy shit.
谢谢 弗兰基
Thank you, frankie.
感谢鼎力相助
For the shot, for the support.
完全是公事公办
Totally justified.
你今天赢了那小混蛋萨克斯
You owned that little shit Saxe today.
可如果你真想和那些家伙竞争
But if you really want to compete with these guys,
你不能有业余生活
You can't have an outside life.
他们有妻子 家庭
They have wives. They have families.
可我们不行
But we can't.
我们必须全天二十四小时待命
We gotta be available 24/7.
你不能有孩子 因为一旦你有了
You can't have kids, because the one time
你的孩子就优先于案子了
You pick your baby over your case,
有些像萨克斯的混蛋就会抢走你的机会
Some asshole like Saxe gets your shot.
他是个混蛋又怎样?
So what he's a dick?
你没在那
You weren't there.
今天柯林斯吃午餐回来
Today collins came back after lunch
亲自邀请你去打牌
To invite you to poker personally.
你却失踪了
You were M.I.A.
对不起 不会再发生了
I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
噢 我知道不会
Oh, I know it won't.
安吉拉 我了解你的档案
I know your file, Angela.
我知道你从哪儿来
I know where you came from,
我知道你多努力才到这里
And I know how hard you worked to get here.
现在代价更大了
The stakes are even higher now.
无论他是谁
Whoever he is,
他不值得毁了你的机会
He's not worth blowing your shot.
我没有男人 弗兰基
There's no man, frankie.
当然 安吉拉
Sure, Angela.
嘿 圣帕特里克夫人 你在这干嘛?
Hey, Mrs. St. Patrick. What are you doing here?
我需要搭车回家
I need a ride home.
没别人时 你可以叫我塔莎
And when we're alone, you can call me Tasha.
没关系 没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
爸爸在这
Daddy's here.
没事啦 亚斯明
It's okay, Yasmine.
爸爸在呢
Daddy's here.